Mr. Heying,
what do you need me for?
Xiao Qi,
that day,
what you told me on the rooftop...
I'm sorry.
I didn't react at the time.
I realized in hindsight
that you were confessing your feelings to me.
But Xiao Qi,
I want to ask you,
are you sure you really like me?
Of course,
Mr. Heying.
In my heart,
you are the most excellent,
the most perfect,
and the absolute best person.
Please believe me.
Xiao Qi,
it's not that I don't believe you.
I just feel
you haven't figured yourself out.
True liking
isn't thinking someone is flawless,
but after you see this person's
vulnerabilities,
flaws,
and even their dark side,
you still feel strongly attracted to them.
But
I don't think you are vulnerable,
or flawed,
or have a dark side.
You were forced by Jinxi to shoot that short drama.
It wasn't your fault.
No.
I do.
I have so many.
You just haven't noticed them,
or perhaps you're unwilling to.
You are just projecting an ideal partner
onto me.
This isn't liking,
and it certainly isn't love.
Xiao Qi,
I believe that one day,
you will definitely understand this.
Isn't this liking?
Don't worry.
I will always be your Mr. Heying.
But I really think
you deserve to experience true love.
A love of mutual discovery
and mutual understanding.
I will accompany you through this confusing stage
until you truly let go.
Okay?
Thank you,
Mr. Heying.
Longing finally turns into a flush of rouge.
Tossing and turning a thousand times,
just for this moment of facing each other.
Across mountains and rivers,
you are by my side.
Stop.
Jinxi,
what are you doing?
I'm
kissing.
Did you even kiss?
No.
Can't we just fake it?
This scene
is a love-pledging scene for Ning Caichen and Nie Xiaoqian.
What I need is authenticity
to push the whole plot to its climax.
Understand?
Understood.
Let's go again.
Ready.
Director, I have an idea.
What is it now?
Can we,
when our lips are very, very close to each other,
use visual effects
to make it look like we're kissing?
What do you think?
This is a musical.
There is no post-production.
Yes.
A stage play.
Go on.
Across mountains and rivers,
you are with me.
Director, I have another method.
Jin Xi,
what exactly do you want to do?
I have two other ways to make it look real.
The first method
is to use my thumb,
placing it against his lips.
It looks very real when I kiss it like this. Look.
How is it?
Or the second method,
using tape.
Stick the tape
on my mouth.
Alright, alright.
Stop doing that.
Take the tape and step down.
Jinxi.
What I need is not for you, Jinxi,
to kiss Bai Feixin.
What I need is Ning Caichen with love,
to kiss Nie Xiaoqian.
Can you show some professionalism as an actor?
Director,
I still don't quite understand.
Heying.
Did you get it?
Understood.
Come.
Do it again.
Thank you, Heying.
Start.
Across mountains and rivers,
you are with me.
Director.
What's wrong with you now?
How can I kiss him when he looks like that?
Am I really that hard to kiss?
No one has ever treated me like this before.
I need to...
calm down a bit.
Five-minute break.
Treating me like this,
is just too much.
Then there's no problem.
Why?
Why
don't I pull away when you kiss me,
but you pull away when I kiss you?
Should I be more assertive?
What?
His leg is injured.
That's how it is.
Jin Xi had spasms due to a muscle contusion in his leg.
He needs to rest for three days.
Is it that stressful to rehearse a kissing scene with me?
It's not your fault.
Don't overthink it.
Jin Xi is injured.
How about each of us buys a bouquet of flowers
to go and comfort him?
I think that works.
Then let's each write him a blessing.
Sure.
We must write it.
When did you guys get so close to him?
Director.
Jin Xi has always had a good relationship with all of us.
He is very nice
and often treats us to snacks.
Two, three.
Come, I'll treat everyone to donuts.
Thank you,
Jin Xi.
Help yourselves.
Thanks, Jin Xi.
Feixin even got fat from eating his donuts.
He's very funny.
Do you still remember
that groundhog joke?
And
the cheesy pickup lines he taught me.
his practical jokes.
Director, didn't you always say we were off-stage?
Then he secretly moved the floor mats in the rehearsal hall
20 centimeters to the right.
What?
He did it.
I told you I didn't stick it crooked.
It made the director scold me all day.
Xiaoqi.
I'm sorry.
I misunderstood you.
Director,
when you were away,
he often took us to play Werewolf.
What?
You all went.
Heying,
you didn't go too, did you?
He had the most fun.
What do you mean I had the most fun?
I got killed on the first night every time.
It was obviously Bai Feixin who had the most fun.
How did I have the most fun?
Wasn't it?
You were all dead,
and I was the werewolf.
Wang Jianshe.
Director, let me tell you.
When Jinxi took us to the club last time,
he was the one who had the most fun.
Why am I the one having the most fun again?
Obviously, Jiao Ye had the most fun.
What?
When did you guys go clubbing?
We're doomed.
This...
Baby.
Let me explain.
On the seventh,
weren't you feeling unwell?
Didn't you say you went to rehearse?
Baby, let me explain.
Which leg did Jinxi injure?
I'll go break his other leg right now.
Director,
I have so many things to tell you.
Talking about Jin Xi,
It still hurts.
What should we do?
Who is it?
Who?
The director.
Bro.
The director is here.
Am I interrupting?
Director,
please come in.
Quick.
Come in quickly.
Come in, please.
Director.
Help him sit down.
Stop jumping around.
Why did you get up?
Have a seat.
Slow down.
I'm here on everyone's behalf to check on you.
These are flowers.
Such beautiful flowers.
And a get-well card.
Thank you, Director.
Wishing Ms. Jin Xi a speedy recovery.
Um, Eason,
is there anything to drink?
We have everything.
Do we have lemon juice?
Any herbal tea?
Yes.
Any Oldenlandia water?
Is the herbal tea sugar-free?
We really don't have this.
Great, I want sugar-free ones.
Go buy two sugar-free drinks.
I'll go then.
Director, please look after him for me.
Okay.
Alright, go on.
Director.
Thank you
for coming to see me.
I'm here representing everyone.
Thank you for representing everyone.
How is your leg?
How was rehearsal today?
I...
I'll speak first.
Director,
how was the rehearsal?
The male lead was absent,
what do you think?
It was unsatisfactory.
Bro.
Guess what.
The vending machine at the door
happened to have two bottles of sugar-free floral tea,
and I bought them both.
Bro.
Director.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
I left my sunglasses at the company.
Could you go get them for me?
Why do you need sunglasses at night?
I...
just want to wear them.
There are several pairs at home.
I'll get them for you.
That pair fits my face shape.
I look good in them.
But your leg is injured like this now.
Wearing sunglasses won't help.
Tomorrow I'll wear my sunglasses in the sun
and go train.
Alright.
Take your time, no rush.
So how did you hurt your leg?
I was just
practicing that scene,
and accidentally injured my leg.
Practicing what scene?
The kissing scene.
With whom?
By myself.
Ah, no,
also with your photo.
No,
also with Bai Feixin's photo.
It's the three of us together,
just...
Alright.
I don't want to hear it.
You don't need to explain.
Oh.
But,
why are you so reluctant
to do a kissing scene?
Because
I...
I don't really want to kiss Bai Feixin.
Why?
Because I want to kiss you.
Well,
the flowers
and the card have been delivered.
I'll take my leave.
Director.
Wish you a speedy recovery.
Come back for rehearsal soon.
Thank you, director.
Thank you, King Luo.
Thank you for taking me to see the sea.
Guys,
let me tell you,
it's getting late.
I can only answer one last question.
'Zai Shui Yi Fang'.
She is a long-time fan of mine.
Let's see what she said.
'Zai Shui Yi Fang' says,
"Hello, Bai Feixin.
About that thing you mentioned before,
he confessed to me.
I explicitly rejected him,
and he agreed to be just regular colleagues.
But I feel like we can never go back to the way we were.
At work,
I can no longer treat him
like a regular colleague.
I feel so awkward right now.
I don't know what to do."
Sister Feixin is telling you very responsibly,
you are overthinking this matter.
When it comes to love,
if you like someone, you must talk directly
and give directly.
Don't beat around the bush.
So what if the result isn't good?
Mr. Heying.
Xiaoqi.
Why do I feel like you're a bit absent-minded?
You really know me.
For so many years,
I've always felt that it's lonely at the top.
But it wasn't until Jinxi appeared
that I realized
a man cannot live without a rival.
Jinxi,
come back.
Ah.
I'm exhausted.
Ms. Qiuyu,
the Demon King isn't here, right?
the director hasn't come back from the Black Box yet?
I just bought all the new things she asked for.
She has a new idea every day.
I don't know why she has so many ideas.
One idea from her,
and I have to run my legs off, you know?
Are you sure she's not here?
She's not.
Since she's not here,
let's have some fun.
The new version of Werewolf.
Read it carefully.
The rehearsal room is the best place to play games.
How many times have I told you?
Whether the director is here or not,
a rehearsal room is still a rehearsal room.
That's a place for rehearsal.
Is it a place to play with these things?
You should rehearse when you are supposed to.
Got it?
Director, you're back.
Have a seat.
I was just scolding them for you.
Even you have been corrupted by Jinxi.
Director,
we need to balance work and rest.
Everyone is tired.
I don't oppose balancing work and rest,
but the schedule for 'A Chinese Ghost Story' is tight.
Now is not the time to play.
Director, the performance is coming up soon.
When will Jinxi be back?
Exactly.
Can he make it in time?
He said he would be back in two days.
He'd better come back soon.
'A Chinese Ghost Story' can't be without Ning Caichen.
Mainly, without him here,
no one buys us milk tea.
No one cracks jokes either.
And the atmosphere in the troupe is so depressing.
Actually,
I don't oppose livening up the atmosphere.
You guys can make jokes.
Don't hold back.
How about this?
I'll start with one.
Ma.
What do you usually think about when you look down?
I...
Are you wondering
if you've gained weight lately,
so your fat
can't fit into the practice clothes?
And the three of you.
Don't think that just because you hid in the back today,
I didn't notice you
were all slacking off.
Is it Mr. Qiu?
After I finish, you tell one.
When will Jinxi be back?
Come on.
Jianshe.
Is your leg feeling better?
It's almost healed.
I'll be able to go back in a couple of days.
Here.
Slow down.
Jinxi,
I really don't understand
how you could
injure your leg practicing a kissing scene.
The other day,
I was at home by myself.
Then I wanted to rehearse
the scene of Ning Caichen and Nie Xiaoqian.
I wanted to find the character's state.
I accidentally fell
and injured my leg.
Jin Xi.
I think
you're just under too much pressure.
I actually can't understand why
you have so much pressure about the kissing scene.
Didn't the director also say
it's not you, Jin Xi, kissing Bai Feixin,
but Ning Caichen kissing Nie Xiaoqian?
Can you understand this?
I don't quite understand.
Let me put it this way, Jinxi.
As actors,
we have two selves.
One is the id,
the other is the superego.
As the id,
we naturally wouldn't just casually
kiss a woman we don't love.
Right?
But as the superego,
we must constantly step into character.
If you fall in love with Nie Xiaoqian,
you have to kiss Nie Xiaoqian.
If you fall in love with a piece of wood,
you have to kiss that piece of wood.
If you fall in love with this land,
you must deeply kiss this land.
Without any distractions
or hesitations.
Do you understand?
Jianshe,
sometimes I really envy you.
I also want to be a professional actor like you.
Jianshe,
can you teach me how to act in a kissing scene?
Okay.
Jianshe,
I didn't mean that.
Sorry for the misunderstanding.
How about this.
Right.
That works too.
Okay then.
Jinxi,
come here,
and follow my lead.
Look at it.
Imagine it as the person you love the most.
Bring out all your feelings and emotions.
Look directly at it.
Approach it gently.
Slowly approach it, bit by bit.
Get close to its lips.
Pay attention,
it's not lips getting close to lips,
but the touching of souls.
Get close and kiss it.
Let it feel the strength and warmth of your lips.
Kiss it.
Kiss it deeply.
Stroke it.
Fall in love with it.
Kiss it.
Why isn't he here yet?
Welcome back, our leading actor.
Welcome.
Director.
My leg is all better now.
Look, I can even do big jumps.
Brother.
Your legs must be numb.
They're numb.
If you stomp, yours will go numb too.
Director.
Thanks to Brother Jianshe,
my kissing skills are now
flawless.
I can kiss Bai Feixin right now.
All right.
No need.
I believe you.
Now that you're back,
we are all very happy.
Let's rehearse then.
Let's start.
Okay.
The male lead walks slowly towards our female lead.
Good.
Keep this pace.
And this emotion.
Very good.
Hold it.
Approach slowly.
Kiss.
Kiss slowly.
So engaged.
Very, very engaged.
Okay, you can separate now.
You can separate now.
Separate now.
This is a rehearsal.
It's for the rehearsal.
Such a big bouquet.
Who sent it?
Could it be a gift to the troupe from a partner company?
No one notified me.
White roses are definitely for a lover.
Right.
You are the July wind,
blowing hotly toward me.
Let me see.
To accompany you through the long years.
That's so cheesy.
July.
Is it for Xiao Qi?
How is that possible?
How could anyone send them to me?
Then it must be from Jinxi's fans.
No.
The ones from Jinxi's fans
are yellow roses.
How do you know?
Because I've talked with Jinxi.
He said he likes yellow roses.
And I like white roses.
I even told the director last time
that the sympathy flowers should be yellow roses.
These are your favorite flowers?
How come I didn't know?
You don't like flowers and plants.
Why would I talk to you about this?
If you don't talk to me, you talk to someone else.
And then have them send flowers to you?
Zhang Wanru, do you have paranoia about being cheated on?
Meng Tejiao, watch your mouth.
All right.
Stop arguing.
These flowers are for me.
What are you arguing about?
Why?
Recently, people have been confessing their love to me in my livestream every day.
My name is Bai Feixin.
My surname is Bai.
And these are white roses.
What are you looking at?
Director.
Jinxi,
come out with me.
Is this the surprise you prepared?
I've already made it very clear.
Doing this is just pointless.
No,
I didn't do anything.
And doing this won't make me happy.
I really don't know what you're talking about.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Such a big bouquet of flowers.
Whose is it?
Why is it here?
Mr. Wu,
your flowers.
Did you order these flowers?
Who are you giving them to?
To the investors.
The address might be wrong.
I thought someone was dating.
I got excited for nothing.
These flowers...
They need frequent watering.
You guys keep rehearsing.
Keep rehearsing.
Why are you here again?
I'm here to apologize.
These are flowers for that.
I'll leave right after.
Apologize?
What are you apologizing for?
It's because of me.
I've been pressuring you too much lately.
That's why you thought I sent the flowers to the rehearsal room.
Besides,
since we've spent so much time together,
I want to apologize for everything.
I'm sorry.
I was the one in the wrong.
But,
you knew
I was mad about the flowers,
and you still brought flowers to apologize.
Yeah.
I crossed the line.
Come in.
Take a seat.
Thanks for the flowers.
I had a bad attitude then.
As long as you're not mad anymore.
I didn't figure out the truth
and just lost my temper at you.
Actually,
I couldn't sleep after I came back.
I wanted to apologize to you,
but I couldn't bring myself to say it.
So I numbed myself with work.
But I ended up writing nothing.
I don't know
what I've been so nervous about lately.
What song are you writing?
It's very important.
The song of Nie Xiaoqian and Ning Caichen's first meeting.
But I've been out of ideas.
You're stuck.
I often get stuck when writing songs too.
So I've figured out
over 10,000 ways to find inspiration.
Want to try?